markologo.com 2013-04-18

# Welcome To Markologo

|   |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---  
 |  |   
|   
---  
|  |   |  |   
---  
   
Marko Logo privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information, how your information is collected, protected and used, which may be updated by Marko Logo from time to time. Marko Logo collects, use and share personal information to help the the website [www.markologo.com](http://www.markologo.com/) work and to keep it safe. Marko Logo will notify any significant changes to its privacy policy by posting notice on the site. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details. 
* **Collection of Personal Information**
  
Information contained by Marko Logo is strictly confidential. Marko Logo does not and will not disclose or share such confidential information to any external organization. Marko Logo may disclose certain personal information as follows: wise made available via the Service. You acknowledge that Marko Logo does not approve or pre-screen Content, but that Marko Logo shall have the right (but not the obligation) in its sole freedom to refuse, delete or move any Content that is available via the Service, for violating the Terms of Use or for any other reason. 

  * by publishing online ads, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers
  * to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or
  * to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.

By having your mobile number listed on Marko Logo, you agree to receive calls/SMS from users who may wish to contact you through the site with respect to the ad posted by you. Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law. Your privacy is very important to us. Marko Logo does not and shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent personal information to third parties without your informed consent. 
* **Using Information**
  
You may use personal information gathered from Marko Logo only to follow up with another user about a specific posting and not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.
*  **Access, Modification, and Deletion**
  
You can access, review, remove or make changes to your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. Marko Logo will delete personal information when no longer required for the purposes described earlier. Personal information is retained as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent spammers from coming back. You need to register in order to post an ad, however you need not register to respond any posted ads on the Website. 
* **Confidentiality of Information**
  
You understand and agree that you have been fully informed that the use of features may lead to publication of any personal information posted by you while using any specific feature on Marko Logo. You further agree that the authenticity of, and consequences from the posting of any personal information are your sole responsibility. You also agree and accept that the terms of the Privacy Policy will be applicable to the use of all features, existing and new. However, you agree and accept that confidentiality of information posted on such features has been waived by you of such features themselves.
*  **Data Security**
  
All information is protected against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.   
   
  |   |
